哈喽,大家晚上好!Hello, good evening, everyone!
哈喽,哈喽,大家晚上好!Hello, good evening, everyone!
哈喽!Hello!
让我看看有没有提早来的小伙伴。Let me see if there are any newbies.
哈喽,哈喽,大家晚上好!Hello, good evening, everyone!
哈喽,哈喽,大家晚上好!Hello, hello, good evening, everyone!
让我看看有没有小伙伴在。Let me see if there are any newbies.
让我看看有没有小伙伴在。
Okay, all I need is junior, and can you guys hear me?
哈喽,听得到吗?Hello, hello, hi, good evening, good evening.
哈喽,哈喽,哈喽,大家晚上好。Hello, hello, good evening.
哈喽,哈喽,大家晚上好。Hello, hello, good evening, good evening, everyone!
哈喽,哈喽, 大家晚上好。Hello, hello, good evening, good evening, good evening.
我们再来等一等,看看有没有小伙伴。Let's wait another bit, see if there are newbies.
Okay, okay.
I didn't turn on the camera today.
Ah, I can't turn on the camera today.
So today you can only hear me talk, but you can't see me.
Hello, hello.
Your name is so hard to pronounce.
Longlong Xiaoxiao.
I don't know you.
Good evening, everyone.
We'll start today's live stream when we reach 7.32pm.
This is Marla's designer.
You came to our live stream and you still want to ask what software this is?
There's our QQ group at the bottom of the screen.
You can enter the group number and password.
Come join our QQ group.
Because the previous QQ group is full now, we have a new QQ group.
Yes, we are mainly a software that can't be solved by friends in the CG industry.
Okay, it's about time.
Let's start today's content.
Before we start today's content,
I want to briefly explain to you that today's content will be divided into two parts.
The first part is that I will briefly explain to you how a motorcycle suit was realized in Marla's designer.
The second part is that I will have a link with our guest Hou Bo.
And then he will share with you how to complete a set of cyberpunk costumes.
So you can look forward to it.
Yes.
And then.
Let's start today's part of my content.
And then I won't turn on the camera today.
Because today I.
Oh, I made an animation with MD, and the clothes fell off.
You can increase the friction rate of the fabric a little bit.
Well, when I talk about the content today, I may speak a little slower.
Because.
Because I just had a surgery on my teeth yesterday.
It's a very urgent situation.
So today I didn't look at the camera because I had to wear an ice bag to cover my face.
Otherwise I can't talk today.
So.
I'll leave if I don't look at it.
Then there's no way.
I can say hello to you guys.
After saying hello, I have to turn off the camera.
Let me take a look at the camera.
Good evening, everyone.
Good evening, I'm going to turn off the camera.
Okay.
So let's start today's content.
Good evening, everyone.
I'm Sherry from Marvelous Designer.
Today I'm going to tell you about how to make a motorcycle suit in Marvelous Designer.
First of all, we're going to.
Let's modify the default model size in our software.
Because the motorcycle suit will be worn on a relatively wide model.
So our default model is relatively thin in size.
So I will edit its size in the model editor.
Then I will import a set of our default clothing.
Use the automatic adjustment panel function.
Then click OK.
Because the default clothing.
Its size is the same as the model we have just adjusted.
This model is not compatible.
So I will use the virtual model.
After adjusting its body shape.
I will use the automatic adjustment panel tool.
To make a adjustment to its size.
If you have any questions, you can also ask in the chat.
In addition to me.
Our chat answer group will continue to answer.
Yes, this is a live broadcast.
I can still see your chat.
Then I will adjust this shoulder plate.
And this sleeve is a adjustment.
Because like a motorcycle suit.
Our default T-shirt.
Its shoulder position is closer to the neck.
So I may extend its shoulder line.
Then I will make a size adjustment to it.
In fact, the first half of this video.
It's mainly a adjustment to the costume.
Then because of the motorcycle suit.
It's still closer to the body line.
So now this costume.
You can see its side is very straight.
There is no wrinkle.
So I may add a point on the side.
Adjust the position of this point.
Then let it have a waist-hugging effect.
Good evening, everyone.
After adjusting such a waist-hugging effect.
I will continue to adjust the size of this plate.
Sometimes I think the waist.
This place may be too inside.
Yes, I recorded the video.
In the introduction.
Then make a adjustment to the side curve.
I will take a look.
Open transparency.
Look at its front or back.
Is there anything wrong?
Or is it too close to the model?
Then I will make a change to it.
After the adjustment.
I will modify the length of the sleeve.
Because the motorcycle suit is usually long-sleeved.
Then I also put the two sides in a little bit.
Then pull the overall length down a little bit.
Good.
Now let's stop and take a look.
There is a problem with my clothes here.
That is, like this one at the bottom of the page.
I have a piece.
It's down.
And then a shoulder point that goes in.
It's sticking out.
Why does it happen when you have a shoulder like this?
The main reason is because of the curve on the sleeve side.
You can take a look.
From the sleeve side to the back.
Do we sew the two ends together?
After that.
After we sew them together.
The shoulder point here will be parallel.
It will appear in this place.
So we have to adjust the curve of this sleeve.
I changed the length of the sleeve here first.
Then make a adjustment to this curve.
In the process of changing the curve.
You have to pay attention.
When you are making a sleeve.
You have to keep this corner is a straight corner.
So that when you sew it with a big body.
It will not appear that corner again.
After opening the model.
You can see.
Like before.
Do we have a protruding triangle in this place?
I made a motorcycle suit.
Let me look for a reference picture.
My last rendering picture.
Let me take a look.
Okay.
The last thing I did was this.
The effect on the picture.
Is a motorcycle suit.
Okay.
Let's continue to explain.
And then.
I will compare.
The length of the sleeve.
Let's see.
Is the length appropriate?
Yes.
Let's see if the length is appropriate.
Sometimes.
Maybe your length is not right.
There will be some unnecessary wrinkles.
And then here.
Why would I go to this curve.
Make it a little flat.
The reason is because.
Like our sleeves.
Especially like a motorcycle suit.
It's more like this.
More like this.
Can highlight the part of the person's body part of the clothing.
Its sleeves are generally relatively flat.
This curve.
And when we just changed.
The length of the sleeve.
Is not it here also becoming a bit smoother?
Then when we a curve becomes relatively smooth.
When the curve of him and you and she have become more smooth.
A bit.
Okay.
Um.
After that.
After that, in order to ensure that the length of these two curves is equal, I will check their length and then change it according to the original curve.
The costume of the He Ju Bian is the second part, which will be explained by another teacher later.
For the Hanfu part, you can take a look at our Hanfu video from the last issue.
And for the parts that are easy to pull apart, it is recommended to reduce its particle diameter and increase its friction coefficient.
After we have adjusted the curve part of the costume, we will make it a lower board and change the side to the curve side.
After we have changed the curve side,
I will use the editor's tool to adjust the curve on the side and change the collar.
Then I will use the version extension tool to extend it along our collar.
Pay attention to the back collar here. I will choose the mirror here.
In this way, there is an advantage in making it.
It is the side of the collar.
The line on the side of the collar is correct.
It means that I am now going to use the version extension tool directly to make a collar for this set of clothes.
For the second teacher, it starts at about 8.30.
But you can also chat with me and see what I am talking about.
Okay, then cut and sew it.
In this way, we will have more collar panels, and then merge them.
Then adjust the point on this curve to make it a collar.
If you are not a fashion professional, if you want to learn how to make a collar,
you can go directly to the website to search for the pattern.
There is also a website called 穿针影线网.
There will be some pattern sharing on it.
Or you can pay attention to our Bilibili Live.
Then use the version extension tool to adjust the collar.
Okay.
After that, um, it's okay.
After that, we can adjust the point of the curve.
Then take a look at its position.
Is it okay? Is it smooth?
Okay.
Next, I am going to make a zipper for it.
For example, we have a sewing line in front of this version.
Then I might have to delete its sewing line first.
Then I will check it in the
I will check how long the zipper I am going to make is.
Because it has to be sewed together with the left two panels.
I will choose these two sides to see its length.
Then I will sew them together.
Then add it to the side tool.
Add it to the side.
After that, we will have this tutorial video.
There is a subtitle in the tutorial video.
And there is no acceleration.
If you watch that video, you might be able to understand it better.
Okay.
After that, I will use the 3D drawing tool to draw directly on the costume.
The most common place to use the 3D drawing tool is to divide the panels and structures on our costume.
As you can see,
when I use the 3D drawing tool to draw on the costume in the 3D space,
there will be some gray lines in the 2D window.
These lines are the effect of my 3D drawing.
Then you can use the internal line tool to draw these lines to divide and edit the costume.
This tool is usually used to cut the costume panels.
And sometimes,
for example,
like this video,
if I want to draw several panels on the shoulder,
if you use the internal line tool to draw, it will be very troublesome.
Sometimes, you can use the 3D drawing tool to draw a general position.
After drawing, you can see that
we can directly turn the 3D line into the internal line.
For the pattern of the panels,
you can search on Pinterest.
For example, if you want to search for a coat,
you can search for coat,
then search for 2D pattern,
2D pattern,
p-a-t-t-e-r-n.
Or you can search directly on Baidu.
For example,
coat,
pattern,
paper pattern.
Then you can find the corresponding pattern.
If you really can't,
you can leave a message in our live broadcast room.
Oh, not live broadcast room,
just leave a message under the official account of Bilibili.
And tell us,
oh, I want to watch this reference video.
Then we will consider everyone's opinions.
I'm going to fall asleep.
Wake up.
Don't fall asleep.
Is it because I talk too passionately?
Be energetic.
Then I will choose these lines.
Then right click,
there is a cut and sew.
In the process of cutting and sewing,
your sewing line may be scattered.
So you have to sew it again.
I might choose to use this multi-step sewing tool.
Because now you can see that this panel is very broken by me.
Then use the multi-step sewing tool,
you can choose one side of the panel first.
Then on the other side,
you can gradually click.
Like this.
For Xiaobai,
You can wait for the comment in this video.
Actually, we mainly wanted to talk to everyone on the live broadcast.
Because if you watch this video directly,
I sometimes operate faster.
But I'm a little too fast to operate.
Maybe it's too difficult to watch.
Add a line.
You can use the built-in multi-layer tool to draw the pattern on the inside of the fabric.
After I divide the fabric into a simple structure, I will merge the excess fabric.
For example, I will merge the shoulder part into a large fabric.
In the case of a motorcycle suit, the shoulder and knee parts are a bit...
I suddenly got distracted. I saw someone asking if black dance is cheap for MD-10.
Yes, it is. MD-10 is on sale every year.
For the part I am working on now,
I am working on this part.
I will adjust the part with sharp corners to make it rounder.
Because I will convert the chest parts into hard parts later.
So if it has sharp corners, it is unreasonable.
Oh, it is free for MD-10. Be careful.
I have already seen your account.
This Bilibili account.
I will search for it.
Our Marvelous Designer has a 30-day free trial.
Then I will apply some fabric to these different locations.
Where is the difference between the official version and the custom version?
One is legal, the other is illegal.
Yes, our Marvelous Designer is from Korea.
Our company is a Korean company.
When applying the fabric to different locations,
we will change the color by the way.
Otherwise, it is not easy to see the division.
It is not easy to see the division.
The reason why we are applying the fabric to different locations is because
we will have to cut a layer out of it later.
If there is an internal line,
it will follow the internal line to make a seam line.
In this way, when you have many layers of cut,
it will be more obvious.
There will be some seam lines.
At the same time, the number of layers of cut depends on the number of people you are using.
I will not reply to questions like this later.
Now I will select all the pieces and cut a layer out of it.
After cutting a layer out of it,
you can see that the back piece itself has a symmetrical line.
You can see that the back piece itself has a symmetrical line.
After cutting a layer out of it,
there may be some seam lines.
I will edit it.
For the seam line between layers,
we will change the seam line type to Turn.
The same for the back pieces later.
After that, I will change the default texture to the leather fabric.
After changing the leather fabric,
I will increase the camera focus level and the camera focus wattage.
If you cannot keep up with the video right now,
you may watch some video of our V-log later.
You may watch some video of our V-log later.
the operation is not accelerated, and then there is a reduction in the thickness of the collision.
As you can see, because now we have this board, it has the top layer and the bottom layer.
If the top layer is relatively small and the bottom layer is relatively large,
there will be some extra wrinkles on the entire clothing.
Using multi-layered clothing, we can make some wrinkle effects like this.
Welcome to the little friends who have just entered the live broadcast room.
Let's get started.
Sometimes our board is used to add details to a specific position.
The outer layer is enlarged.
I use shrinkage.
This is the effect of shrinkage in the model editor.
Then we will use the ruler tool to add details along the position we want to add wrinkles.
Use the ruler to make an addition.
After adding the correct value of the ruler, we will default to this grid area.
This grid will become larger.
In Marvelous Designer, when you combine a larger piece with a smaller piece,
the larger piece will form some wrinkles and stack in a small piece.
No, I'm not working overtime.
Today is in the afternoon.
If you have any questions during the use process,
you can go to the QQ group in the bottom of the live broadcast room.
You can chat with us.
Or if you just want to have some questions, you can also ask.
Then it's the same as our costume.
Put on a pair of pants.
Then use this.
Use the outer layer of the board to make a belt.
Then there is our automatic adjustment board function.
To make it a size that fits the model.
Like the top.
We.
Oh, yeah, I said it wrong.
You can just find me.
Yeah.
Isn't it fast to sound?
For the naked shoes,
after you choose a pair of shoes,
click the right arrow to delete shoes.
That's it.
For the pants,
we use a change in length.
You can directly change the length of a line.
If you choose Bose,
it will start from the middle and go to both sides.
This is the edge of Sodam.
And then for pants like leather pants,
it's.
Oh, yeah.
When you're adjusting the shoes,
you have to choose the right shoes.
Then right click.
Don't just select the model and then delete.
Oh, and then the pants side.
It's the same as the top.
You can use the 3D drawing tool.
You can draw some cut lines on our clothing.
Okay.
And then I might go to the inside of the line.
And then I'll cut it for him.
Make a zipper.
In fact, if you want to make a motorcycle suit,
the focus is not on how to cut these plates.
But it's about how you.
How to do it.
For example,
it's like gloves and breath.
This kind of accessory is more important.
Like making pants.
I'm sure you all know how to make this effect.
Okay.
And then it's time for us to make this.
It's time for the breathing effect.
Okay.
Let's draw a line first.
Then we're going to start doing this round breath.
Shoes are built by other modeling software.
You can use the form of a virtual model to lead to Marvelous Designer.
You can also directly use the material to make some shoes in Marvelous Designer.
It's okay.
As long as you watch more of our post-production videos,
you can definitely learn.
If you can't learn,
if you can't learn,
you can chat with us.
Or come to the QQ group to find us.
Okay.
And now I'm going to make him a fur to the outside of this.
Oh, make hair with fabric.
That's what I suddenly came up with.
Because.
How do you get on the board?
After you select the board,
there is a right-click to add to the outside.
That function will.
Will directly put a board quickly to the outside of another board.
Of course we can add a group.
Our second group.
Our second group is for some new friends.
Come and see.
There are a lot of post-production videos.
We really have a lot of videos.
And we have P1 and P2 live.
P1 is generally a live video.
And then P2 is usually that.
Is the later learning.
Video of the classic version of learning.
In the case of the WeChat group,
there is no one at home.
This member of the group.
It's too inconvenient to manage the WeChat group.
Okay.
Then we now add a board to the outside.
The physical properties of this board are also leather.
But.
It will reduce its bending strength a little bit.
Then we will add some pressure to it.
Let it.
Let it add to the outside.
Mr. Man Ding.
Which is Man Ding?
Mr. Man Ding is very famous.
Then we will sew a rectangular edge.
Use it to make this soft edge transition.
Because if you sew a rectangular edge directly,
it may not be very good.
Hold this effect.
Is the effect of breathing.
Then we may sew a rectangular edge in the middle.
Sew it up.
In fact, it's like making a cake.
You can see it when you add it to the outside.
Then start the simulation.
And let's reduce its particle strength and pressure.
Oh, increase its pressure.
In fact, it's like using fabric to build a.
A folding board like this.
You see.
You have to reduce some bend strength.
Otherwise, in the position of this border,
it will have a very obvious border.
Okay.
Claw.
Claw also has a live broadcast today.
If you often use Claw in the video,
you can also see it later.
The live broadcast on our Claw side.
Because today is just the right time.
Okay.
Then like.
Um.
The side of our knee board.
If.
Because.
You can take a look.
Um.
I have this one.
This circle of boards.
It's longer.
And then a board like this.
It needs a shorter transition.
To be able to transition to a more smooth curve effect.
I don't know.
Okay.
Um.
Why the Claw is so consistent.
Did you.
put that.
The weight that the Claw itself carries.
has been reduced.
You might have adjusted the weight to zero.
When your weight is zero.
Um.
Your board.
It'll be.
It might be floating in the air.
Of course.
If you guys want to do it.
If you want to do some.
The effect of floating materials.
Um.
You can.
A little bit.
Wait a second, I suddenly realized that I didn't open my software.
Let me open an empty software, let's continue.
Oh, so that's how it is.
And then because, like everyone else, when you're making this fabric,
there's one thing you must remember,
which is, especially for places like this that will connect together,
you must make this corner close to 90 degrees.
Imagine that you put two pieces of fabric together,
if one is a corner, and the other is also a corner,
if two corners are sewn together, they are still sharp,
they are not flat.
You must make sure that the two are sewn together,
the position is straight, and the position is flat.
This is also what we talked about in many of our teaching videos.
And then, like now,
this piece of fabric,
the side is bent into a curve,
and then when you sew the two sides together,
it becomes more smooth.
Of course, it's still a corner,
sometimes it's still an inward corner.
What's the difference between MD and Claw?
In Marvellous Designer, there's no guide,
there's only one side,
and the other side,
but in Marvellous Designer, there's no guide.
For MD,
it's mainly for people in the CG industry,
a software that can't be solved.
As for Claw,
it's for the clothing industry,
it's a software that can produce the actual design.
For example, Claw has some rendering and other functions,
but there's none in Marvellous Designer.
Yeah, yeah,
more corners equals more corners.
Yeah.
Looks like everyone knows math very well.
And then,
I'll reduce the strength of the 3D sewing line,
so that you won't see the sewing line
if it's in an over-the-top position.
Now, like the knee position,
can you tell that it looks like a bulging circle?
Well,
Ah, the guests will be here at 8.30pm.
Really, what game do you guys want to use our software for?
Okay, for the clothes here, we will give it a layer, so that it can be worn outside the pants.
Is it equal to the corner? I can't remember if it's called the crotch or the corner.
Oh, no, our guests are more professional than me.
For my shoulders, I also made it.
Today's guest is called Hou Bo, MD is not available yet.
But I'm not sure about next year, but this year is not available for the time being.
Maybe next year.
Okay, for the shoulders, I went to understand the structure of the suit.
Usually, there will be a layer here.
And then, outside of this layer, there will be another layer.
It's not AG, it's not Annie Raider today.
It's Hou Bo today.
What about elementary school students?
Elementary school students can't do it.
It's against the law to hire a tailor.
Okay, for the shoulders, if your bending strength is too high,
Then this plate itself is very hard.
You can't hold it up easily.
So you may have to lower the bending strength a little bit.
Then let the curve on the side be smoother.
What do you usually want to know about Marvelous Designer?
Or functions that are not very clear?
You can ask in the chat now.
This is how it works,
After the fabric is sewed outside,
It will have a bulging position.
Okay, sometimes the back piece has a position that interests the interlocking,
You can take a look.
Do these line intentionally intersects or intersect?
If you don't understand,
It's a good idea to have a look at our preliminary tutorial video.
I recommend watching our preliminary tutorial video.
There is a door entrance.
The new users enter the door can first enter the door.
入门可以先从那个视频开始看,每个版片都弄得好专业,我没有弄得很专业呀,就是只是说大家平时在做衣服的过程中,你需要先去了解一下,尤其是我经常会上淘宝上面去搜这种类型,比如说我今天要做摩托车服,我就会看一个淘宝,然后到淘宝里面去搜一下。
好,现在呢,我就给他的裤子换了一个叫塔夫绸,这个属性,面料物理属性的话呢,是大家以后肯定会经常用到的,它是经常会用来做一些冲锋衣,这种褶皱还是比较细碎的版片,上面会用塔夫绸。
那大家如果对这个物理属性不了解的话,可以看一下我们之前的其他教学视频。
有一个是关于我们面料物理属性的那个视频,那个视频里面的话会有,就是跟大家讲解。
还有一个叫中文物理预设,没有啊,面料描述的话,有一期视频叫中文物理预设,还是叫,应该是叫中文物理预设,那一期视频里面有讲怎么去替换这个面料的。
好。
之后像裤子的侧边的话呢,我可能会给它应用一个弹性,就是让侧边抽一个百分之九十八、九十九的弹性。
开启弹性之后呢,它侧边就会有一些细小的褶皱出现了。
否则侧边的话它就是不够平整嘛,它就是会太平整,就是不够有那样的细节褶皱了。
。
好,像裤子这边的话呢,可能也会给它用一些违向缩略啊,修改一下面料物理属性啊之类的。
对。
大家平时其实可以多逛逛我们B站的视频,还是有蛮多的。
。
电脑啥配置啊,我录视频的时候呢,我的电脑应该是i7还是i9。
i7配的2060Ti的卡。
好像。
。
嗯,能,但是想学的萌新的话不要用MD4,软件的话肯定是越新越好用的。
当然如果bug很多的话,那当我没讲,但是一般来说软件都是越新越好用的。
对,电脑不好的话你可能就得用D版本。
但是用D版本的话呢,虽然核心内容就是没什么不一样,但是我们现在录的视频基本上都是MD9,MD10它配套的嘛。
有一些功能可能D版本里面是没有的,这个可能要注意一下。
现在呢,我接下去因为要做手套嘛。
嗯,对,现在因为我要做手套,所以我要给它的袖子这里应用一个缩滤,让它收紧。
你可以看到当我们缩滤降低的时候,这个袖子就收紧了。
接下去就是要制作一个手套。
那手套这边为了方便制作,我把它透明度降低。
这样你把这个版片盖在手部的时候呢,你就可以沿着手部去绘制这个手套形态了。
好,谢谢hohoho以后的关注,谢谢。
大家平时有什么想了解的内容啊什么的,也可以现在在弹幕里面提问。
做手套其实也挺方便的,你就沿着这个模特的手部曲线。
然后因为我开的是,我开了个透明度嘛。
然后你就沿着这个手部的曲线去画一下。
当然我这里是没有预留空间的。
那我在后期去沿着这个图形绘制的过程中呢,我可能就会有意的让它就是尽量是差不多宽的。
因为你现实生活中不可能你的这个小指跟中指差这么多嘛。
对啊,你做手套或者说你在做一些衣服的时候你都可以用这个方法。
粘衬条是用在你不希望那一条边进行变形的位置。
嗯,对,做鞋子也是一样的方法。
好。
手套完成了一个部位之后呢,你要把它的粒子间距降低,否则它的曲线过度就不原顺。
而且像手部这种网格本身,就是模特这个部位的网格本身就比较多的情况下,你在这个,因为软件它创建出来的版片它的粒子间距是很大的。
因为软件它创建出来的版片它的粒子间距是很大的。
嗯,有可能在手指这个位置呢,就会出现模特的网格穿出来的问题。
好。
然后我还会表面间距,呃,就是表面翻转一下这个版片。
这个手套我一定要保证它的两个发线方向是相对的。
之后就用3D划线切一下。
呃大家肯定看不懂我现在在干什么,过一会儿你就看懂了。
就是一般来说这个手套都是有厚度的嘛,它的侧边是有一条边的,现在我们就是要把这条边切出来。
This is so smart, how did you know?
I didn't expect you to guess it before I even started.
So smart.
For this kind of joint, the seam line, and the line on the side of the finger,
they all have a side, so we need to cut this side out first.
Then we'll draw a rectangular edge, and sew it together with our gloves.
If you find it too much of a hassle to sew it in a 2D window,
you can sew it in a 3D window.
After sewing,
use the side-to-side tool to sew this edge near the gloves.
Then the other side is also operated in the same way.
If you don't know which edge to sew in a 2D window,
you must use a 3D sewing machine.
This is our MD8's new feature.
Or is it MD10? Or is it MD9?
I suddenly forgot.
In short, this feature allows you to sew in a 3D window
when you are not sure how to sew in a 2D window.
If my speech is too quiet, you can tell me.
Because my teeth are a bit sore right now,
so my speech might be a bit quiet.
Well, it seems that Aiya Aiya He He He knows our software very well.
After that, I will add a fixing pin on these two panels,
to fix its position,
and then sew the other panels, especially the thumb, together.
I used leather material for the gloves.
It is not easy to deform.
It is easier to maintain the original shape.
I usually sew a little bit, then model a little bit,
and then add some fixing pins to prevent it from deforming.
In this way, the overall shape of the gloves is completed.
After that, we will continue to add some pins,
to move the position of the gloves.
Because the fixing pins can be fixed in certain parts of the grid,
there will be some screenings.
For example, later, when Mr. Hou Bo talks about
some projects related content,
he may have the strength to work with the screenings.
Thank you for your attention, LPD88.
Thank you.
If you have any questions during the process of making clothes,
if you can't think of anything right now,
you can add a QQ group first,
and then ask us in the QQ group.
Basically,
we are here from Monday to Friday every day.
And then on weekends,
we usually watch the QQ group.
But as long as you mention the question,
we will definitely reply.
It's just the time difference.
Now I may add some fixing pins.
The QQ group is at the bottom.
Because this is the second group,
I can't remember the group number.
At the bottom of the live broadcast you are watching now,
there is our QQ group at the bottom.
The QQ group at the top,
there is our option at the top.
You can add one,
or you can add a Antenna in the QQ group.
So,
you can make a QQ group.
Next,
I will show you how to make a QQ group.
I will show you how to make it.
First,
let's make a QQ group.
We need a QQ group.
In this QQ group,
we are not going to make a QQ group.
Let's say you want to make something like this.
Let's say you want to make a QQ group.
For example, you wear gloves, and the rest of your fingers are worn out.
Only here it flies out, right?
Then we may use the selection grid tool to select some grid at the 2D window.
After selecting, check the location of this grid.
Then use the positioning tool to paste this part of it,
and then generate a fixed needle to open the simulation,
and then it will be worn up.
After it's worn up, I'll adjust it again.
Hmm, yes.
But I can only say congratulations to those friends who joined the first group,
because the first group is already full,
it's no longer open.
So now we're opening the second group.
There aren't many people in the second group yet,
so the friends who joined the second group are now the elders of the second group.
After that, it might be,
we'll do some cutting in the middle of the fingers.
After cutting, we'll align the position of the outline of the board.
Yes, now there are only more than 100 people in the second group.
The first group can add people,
but because the second group has already been opened,
the first group is temporarily not open.
When the first group of friends,
for example, has more space,
then it will be open.
Because to be honest, there are more people in the first group now.
Sometimes there are some friends who might have a water group,
but the second group usually doesn't have a water group problem.
Then, like the gloves here,
I also cut a layer out of it,
and then I'm going to make a cut to make some structures.
So I'm going to make some structures.
The first group,
I'm going to make a cut on the top of the first group,
and then I'm going to make a cut on the bottom of the second group.
The second group,
I'm going to make a cut on the top of the first group.
So, this is the process that I usually use when I make gloves.
I use transparent plated,
and then I use fixed needles to adjust its position.
Then draw some inner lines,
to separate it.
That's so annoying.
Because you care about the members, don't you?
If you don't dare to randomly choose the details, you can go to the members and ask.
For example, you can say, I want a very detailed wrinkle effect right now, how should I choose it?
If it doesn't work, you can talk to me or Jimmy to ask.
But it's more convenient to recommend directly to the members.
As for the gloves, I'm going to add a layer of cologne to this version.
After the cologne is done, I'm going to do...
Qin Hao! Qin Hao is at the bottom.
Our little Dijin, let our little assistant answer your question.
Because I can't remember this Qin Hao.
I'm going to draw an oval in the middle, and I'm going to sew the oval on top of the gloves.
After adding it to the outside, when I do it, I always change it here and there.
For example, now you can see that this is our bottom layer, and this is the outer layer.
When you mix a wider layer and a narrower layer together,
when you mix them together, you get this wrinkle effect.
This is the effect of the motorcycle gloves.
For the middle part, I'm going to add some pressure.
After adding pressure, you can zoom in a little bit.
It will pop up like this.
It has a structure that pops up like this.
Welcome to the new friends in the live stream.
I see you.
The new friends are called
Raise the lantern and fight with you.
Hello, hello.
Because now I have a larger circle and a smaller circle mixed together,
and then there's the influx,
so this version will pop up.
This is going to go up higher.
So here I am.
Now I'm going to add the levels.
I'm going to add the layers after this.
I will apply this layer to my gloves.
And then when the levels are higher,
I'll enlarge the inner layer,
and you will have a virtual effect.
But you must have encountered,
for example, when your gloves are closer to the outside,
even if there are layers,
the clothes inside you will still be worn out.
You can take a look at it.
I think there will be a problem with the wear after a while.
For example, when I change the shrink rate inside to 100,
you can see that there is still a crack, and it will still wear out.
The reason is because the inside of the board is larger.
Yes, there will be a problem with the draw.
How do we solve this situation?
At the beginning, I tried to use the friction coefficient to make a constraint on this board.
After that, I decided to use the fixer to fix it.
I will find the position of this small circle,
and then use the fixer to fix it on the virtual model.
Use this tool to fix the whole edge to the virtual model.
After that, you will not have this problem when you turn on the simulation.
In fact, just imagine that you wear a sweater in winter,
and then wear gloves.
When you wear your gloves up,
your sweater may also be pulled up by you.
Because it has the problem of mutual friction,
it will be unstable and shake.
After you use the fixer to fix the position of this edge,
you will not have this problem anymore.
Generally speaking, you will not have this problem anymore.
Moreover, when you change the motion,
when a fixer is fixed on the virtual model,
it will also make a change with this motion.
After that, I will change the constraint.
It may be completed.
Finally, the edge can also be fixed.
Finally, I will change the motion.
You can see that although the motion is changing,
the gloves and the clothes are also changing together.
In fact, in the end,
I want to use the orange color of Marvelous Designer.
But in the end,
you will find that I don't like to do colorful things.
I like to match black and white.
So in the end,
the final product,
not the product,
but the rendering,
I still use black and white.
And then,
for the cross section,
sometimes I will
adjust it with this ruler.
Because sometimes,
for example,
if I have less wrinkles now,
I may add a little bit of shrink.
Let me show you the final project file.
Let me take a look.
There won't be anything in this project file, right?
There won't be any sensitive information, right?
I don't think so.
Who said that Marvelous Designer's orange color is the orange color of the wine?
What does this mean?
Isn't the orange color of the wine all broken?
I want to use the ruler.
I'll show you later.
Let's take a look at the final project file first.
Okay.
Wait a minute, everyone.
Wait a minute.
I think this will work.
Actually, it's fine.
This is the final project file.
Mainly because the one I am using now
is not the one I use often.
So you might see that my project file might be a little bit lagging.
And this computer is also not working for some time.
I don't know if it's going to work
Wow, no way
Let me see
Did any of you guys tell me that you guys are still watching my live stream?
Hello, hello, is my live stream still on?
Oh, it's fine, it's fine, you scared me
Oh, I thought my live stream was turned off
Help
You scared me
When I saw the blank screen, my heart was broken
This is the last project file
As you can see, my outfit doesn't have a lot of wrinkles
I didn't hide anything
It might be because of its small wrinkles
And when the cologne is applied to the outer layer, I added some soly to make it look more wrinkly
The computer I use is an Intel one, not an AMD one
This is the final result
And then, some of you guys just asked me
What's the use of a ruler?
Well, a ruler is like this
For example
For example, I have a board
Oh, can it not jump out again?
There will be some problems with the GPU resolution
We will invite the next part later
It starts at around 8.30
The information about theavil-
That doesn't say anything
Wow, how would it do this?
Not at all
That doesn't say anything
For example, I have a panel, right?
I'll add twoizza
I'll add twozza
Wow, looks like it won't die
Wow, this is hard
Studioり
Source
For example, let's open a grid display.
Now, is my grid a negative number?
When I use a negative number,
and I make a negative grid for the middle one,
its grid will shrink.
Do you see that?
The grid of the middle one will become smaller,
and this one will be closed.
But if I draw a grid with a positive number in the middle,
can you imagine what will happen?
Let's guess.
I used a negative number just now.
When I use a negative number, the grid of the middle one shrinks.
Now I use a positive number to draw a grid in the middle.
What will happen to the orange part?
Can you tell me?
The grid of the middle one shrinks.
Its grid will become bigger.
Let's compare.
How can it become smaller?
Of course, it's because it's opened.
Did you hear carefully?
6209327
Yes, it will expand.
Its grid will become bigger.
So, in a piece of fabric,
In a piece of fabric,
when there is no grid itself,
it may be flat.
Right?
Then when you add this positive number,
it will become bigger.
It will create a fold.
This is a common method of using a grid.
That is, if we take a piece,
for example, this piece has a fold.
Let's assume that its fold is here.
Then you use a negative grid to adjust it.
Adjust it like this.
Its fold will be smaller.
And then you spread it out again.
Its fold will become smaller and smaller.
But you shouldn't have one fill in with positive and one with negative.
Otherwise, it will become like this.
I am painting it now.
It is like this.
If your fabric has a lot of folds,
and you want to spread it out,
then it is like this.
If you want to spread it out,
this is how it works.
龟拔 is a word used in the fashion industry.
龟 means a turtle.
For example, if you have wrinkles on your sleeves,
you can smooth the wrinkles with a turtle.
拔 means...
Oh, the sleeves are usually not covered with a turtle.
It's the pants.
拔 means to make a piece of fabric bigger.
用韵抖
It's hard to explain.
It's hard to understand.
比如说你用韵抖去打蒸汽的时候, For example, when you use a turtle to make steam,
你可以一边运一块布, you can move a piece of cloth,
然后一边用手把这个布拉大, and use your hand to stretch the cloth.
就是韵抖。 It's called 韵抖.
所以其实有很多小伙伴会管龟拔叫韵抖工具。 That's why a lot of people call龟拔叫韵抖工具.
哦,现在八点半了,我来看看。 Oh, it's eight and a half now. Let me see.
我来连线一下我们的老师。 Let me connect with our teacher.
大家有其他关于MD的问题呢, If you have any questions about MD,
可以过一会儿到我们老师演示完毕之后提出,可以过一会儿到我们老师演示完毕之后提出, you can ask questions after the teacher's presentation.
好不好? Okay?
我来连线一下老师。 Let me connect with our teacher.
稍等一下哦。 Wait a moment.
大家要记住,等一下来的老师叫侯博。 Remember, the teacher who will come later is called Hou Bo.
一定要记住哦,大家要懂礼貌。 Remember, you have to be polite.
对,大家要记住,我们等一下老师连线进来。 Yes, you have to remember that the teacher will come later.
好。 Okay.
侯博老师, Let me connect with our teacher.
侯博老师呢,是一个非常专业的老师。 He is a very professional teacher.
我不辛苦,我不辛苦,我还在的。 I'm not tired, I'm not tired, I'm still here.
哈喽,哈喽,老师,老师。 Hello, hello, teacher, teacher.
喂。 Hello, hello.
喂,哈喽,哈喽。 Hello, hello.
那,好。 Okay.
老师,你现在可以跟我共享一下你的屏幕啊。 Teacher, can you share your screen with me now?
我们就到了,对,就到了您这边的部分。 We are now at your side.
好的,好的。 Okay, okay.
你现在可以看见画面吗? Okay.
稍等一下,我来把这个...喔,好了。 Oh, can you see the screen now?
稍等一下,我来把这个...看一下。 Let me take a look at this.
哦,好的。有的,有的。 Oh, okay. I got it.
哦,那,那我这边就开始了。 Okay.
嗯,好的,好的。 Yeah, okay, okay.
哦,哈喽,哈喽,大家好,然后... Hi, hello, hello, everybody, and...
Let me introduce myself first. My name is Pan Xiteng.
Pan Yiteng is my real name.
My internet name is Hou Bo.
I am currently a freelancer.
My work is related to... Is the volume too low?
Hello?
Oh, hello, hello, teacher. I increased the volume of your voice.
It should be fine now.
Okay, okay. I will continue.
I am now a visual artist.
I also do some concept design for games and videos.
When I first graduated, I was in the game industry.
I also did some...
I was interested in game development.
I am also an independent game developer.
But later on, I was involved in some...
I found out that making games was still a difficult thing.
So I turned to focusing on making works.
And I also do some collaborations with platforms like AboutCJ.
To talk about...
To record some courses.
That's about it.
And then...
Here are some of my personal masterpieces.
Mainly...
There are more works on Behance and Artstation.
If you want to know more about my works,
you can check out my personal masterpieces.
And then...
This is a rough introduction of my works.
This is a demo of a game I made.
And then...
I made a basic character run and jump.
It's like a little
like a little man-o-o.
It's like a little man-o-o.
And then...
After this work is done,
I started to do some visual and concept design things.
And then...
These are some of the projects I designed.
Mainly based on science fiction.
Because I actually...
I really like science fiction.
So in this aspect,
I pay more attention to a lot of things.
This is a CD cover.
And this is a personal work.
And then...
Occasionally, I will draw some small blueprints myself.
I will draw some small blueprints myself.
And then today,
I will share some examples of
how to make the clothes
that are included in the MV of He Ju Bian.
And then, because the pre-made video
can't be shown in normal quality,
so I will show it to you in the main page.
The network is not very good
I will show you the video
This is what the video looks like
Let's go back to the PPT
The clothes and the materials for the cloak
are all completed in MarbleEase Designer
including some animations for the final resolution
So today I will mainly share with you
the general process of making this project
Let's get started
For this project
When I first started
I had to have a basic human model
Because the client
doesn't have a very high requirement for the character
So the client doesn't have a very high requirement for the character
So when I was working on this project
I didn't design the character's appearance
I just created a basic human model
from the Dev Studio
But the character's appearance
was customized according to my own needs
This was done with another software
called FaceGen
I will not go into details in this part
And then
This model
Basically
Because it was made from the Dev Studio
It will have some basic stickers
Like color stickers
And some hair lines
And auto stickers
So basically
Based on these stickers
I made some skin materials in the CC
And then
This model
After making this model
It will look like this
Sorry
This is a shortcut
After making this model
It will look like this
It is a basic APOS
Because it is tied to the back
So it is connected to the shoes
And it is done
For the feet
This part should be
Let's take a look at the model
The feet are complete
And then
The material
Is made from
Octane
Basically, I used the basic materials provided by the developer to create a 3S texture.
Let me show you.
Okay, I'll wait for you to send it to me.
No, no, no, it's okay.
It's okay now.
Just refresh it.
Okay, so I don't need to do anything here?
Yes, it's okay, you can keep talking.
Okay, then I'll pay a little attention here.
I'll just show you the head.
You can see that there is a very clear separation line here.
Because the head is...
I customized it a little bit.
Although the quality is not particularly good,
but basically it can be seen.
Then this basic model...
I'll stop here.
After the basic model is done,
then...
I'm going to start making the materials.
But because...
Let's switch to the back.
Because this is an APOS.
It can be worn.
But for that...
At that time, we wanted to show it.
Just don't look so stiff.
Just want him to do a natural hammering action.
So it's going to let this character
enter a binding process first.
Then after binding,
it's probably like this.
then...
That is to say, this...
I will communicate with the binding side.
Then let him provide me with a simple animation.
It's this hand from APOS.
Gradually...
Transformation to a state of natural hammering.
So it's convenient for me to show it to him after he's dressed.
Including...
You can see this APOS is also...
It's probably like this.
Then...
Then this...
When this model is made,
I usually make it in ABC format.
Then you put this animation range in there.
After it goes in, it will...
It doesn't seem to have any special settings.
Anyway, I remember it seems like...
MD supports ABC quite well.
You can just open it and use it.
Then it will...
I will...
I will enter a...
A fabric production.
The fabric production...
Basically, I'm from...
Uh...
It's just...
One version by one.
It's this kind of...
It's a step-by-step process.
Because the client sometimes...
It will involve...
Suddenly...
You need a version you've done before.
So I...
I'm used to keeping...
This kind of file at every stage.
Then...
Uh...
MDA is like this.
MDA is actually...
It's a bit of a shame to say.
I haven't studied it very systematically.
So it's usually...
Uh...
It uses a few more basic functions.
Then it involves some...
For example...
Uh...
In the production process,
If there is an actual problem,
I'm...
I'm going to learn it now.
Then...
It's...
About software.
There may not be too much...
Uh...
Too many things to tell you.
You can go and see some...
It's...
There are actually a lot of these...
Uh...
Tutorials.
Then...
Uh...
I...
I'm just...
It's mainly for this project.
Some of the process...
Uh...
Share with you.
And then...
Like me at first.
Because I'm actually not a...
Uh...
Fashion background professional.
So it's like this.
This kind of thing on the board.
In fact, I'm also...
Uh...
I'm completely from...
Purely from the point of view of art.
That is to say...
Look at this picture.
He just has to wear it.
Basically in line with...
One of the effects I want.
Just OK.
Uh...
And then basically...
Is...
Will use a few common tools.
Is this...
To give him...
To build this board.
And then...
Uh...
Oh...
The computer is a bit slow.
The computer is so slow today.
Oh...
It may be because...
The computer is so slow today.
Oh...
It may be because...
We started shooting that...
Tencent.
One screen, right?
Yes.
Start recording screen.
Oh.
Will...
Yes.
Because there's a live broadcast.
Oh.
And then...
Uh...
Will use...
This...
Output tools.
With some added points...
Or...
Uh...
Editing番戸.
Or this...
To coordinate.
Let it create a picture.
The piece like this is...
First to...
Uh...
Insert a picture,
a picture.
This is...
I first gave it a left-sided version, and then I made some of the legs that I wanted to make round.
I usually do this, I first draw out the whole piece of fabric.
What you see now may have a lot of very detailed versions, but when I first made it, it was actually a big whole.
It's a bit like a chain.
After I put the whole piece of fabric on it, I felt that it was almost done.
The proportions and the width of the fabric, that's when I started to draw out the details.
Like how to cut it into a few pieces, or how to cut it.
And then, let's take a look at the next one.
And then, like this helmet, because when I make the next version, I will need to make some of the structure of the hat and the cape.
Then there will be a collision with his head, so I just put this helmet directly into it.
But this helmet, in fact, my way of operating it is more violent.
Because when the helmet finally falls out,
Let me show you, the face is still quite high.
I'll just give you a quick look.
And when I brought it in, the model in MD should still be a triangle.
So when I was calculating, I also encountered some problems.
That is, it may have some cross-interference, or maybe it's because the face is too high.
And then like this.
Yes, this is basically the same.
That is, the face after it was created is still quite a lot.
But like this tube on both sides, because the modification has been removed.
So compared to this model, it may still have a little less face.
And then, this project is not going to do the replacement collision.
That is, for this model, like before, it may be.
For example, when the face of this model is too high, it will be very long.
Then I may.
I will make this high film and make it into a low film.
Then, but the face still needs to be a little bit.
Because if the face is particularly low, it will also form the feeling of the material of the grid.
So you still have to make it a little bit rounder.
Then pour it in and make it a collision.
And then the shoes, because it will also have some interaction with the material.
So I'll find it for now.
I found a pair of material shoes to replace it.
And then this cape, because it's on the outside.
So I'm basically going to put it in first.
For example, if you want to adjust it again, you'll hide the cape first.
And then if it's OK inside, I'll activate the cape again.
And then like the beginning, I'm here.
It's just using his default example.
This is the value of 20.
I'm going to solve it like this.
Because the graphics card should be cpu, it should be.
Because my cpu is actually general.
So it's just a little bit better to solve it.
And then when it comes to the final output, it may give it a value of 5.
And then the result of the calculation is relatively clear.
But if it's still zoomed in, there will still be some.
Uh, that's what this is.
Uh, it's this, uh, uh, this kind of uh, it's not particularly smooth.
But that's how I solved this problem.
Is if you're going to give her this face number up to a very high to uh, violent that kind of
calculation, one is a very long time.
Another one is to say, sometimes if it's not the kind of big blood, then you can't see
that much details.
So I usually basically give it a 5 when it's out, and then put it in the ccd
to give him a smooth.
Uh, basically, you can.
Yeah, yeah.
It looks like it's almost smoothed out visually.
And then, let's take a look at the next few versions.
And then in this version, I basically started to do some...
I roughly divided the colors of the fabric.
And then in the future, when I draw the material in this SP,
I basically do the material according to this division.
And then this...
Because of the binding problem,
my character's mind is not on the ground.
So there will always be some problems at that time.
For example, the fabric.
The person is in this position.
But I hope that the fabric will naturally come down.
But there will be a collision with the ground.
And then the tearing is very serious.
And then I need to...
Let me think about it.
I forgot where it is.
I need to turn off this ground collision for it.
Ah, the simulation attribute.
Yes, in this one, right?
No, you can see another simulation attribute in the 3D window.
Ah, yes, it's here.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
And then I will put this...
Let me look it up.
Ah, there is a paper surface.
Yes, there is a collision.
I will turn this off.
After turning it off, there will be no collision with the ground.
And then...
Because the character I played before
was walking on the ground.
And there will be a feeling of wind inside.
So it's...
It's pretty good to turn on the wind model that MD brought with him.
It's in this...
Ah, I forgot where it is again.
There is a wind controller in this environment.
And then after the display, there will be some parameters in it.
I basically just adjust the strength and the airflow.
These two things go together.
And then...
Basically, after this step,
I will go into this animation
to do a simple simulation of it.
Take a look at the feeling of this material.
And then at this stage,
actually, at this stage,
actually, this character has not been binded yet.
And then this character...
The animation he is using now is in this...
What is it called?
Adobe has a self-binding website to complete it.
It's equivalent to a preview effect.
And then I took a look at some of the feelings of this material.
Including in this...
In this file that is more custom-made in the back.
Is the website you are talking about MAKESUMMER?
That is...
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, it's a...
How long is this?
Oh, yes.
Because I feel that sometimes,
if the requirements are not particularly high,
the kind of binding is quite practical.
Um.
Uh, and then when I did this step,
I changed a lot.
It's their style.
Because the client wanted this kind of oblique feeling.
And then I changed it.
Including this...
Uh, it's about the final...
This...
At the time of the resolution,
I will adjust the physical properties of this material.
Uh, because my English is not very good.
So at that time,
I went to look at it with this translator.
What kind of material do you want?
Just go in there.
Uh, actually test this effect.
And then...
Uh, after this step,
Basically, it's...
This file should be used in the end.
Uh, what is this?
Oh, I see that.
Then I will insert it to the assembly.
Then...
There is a big change.
But in the end,
the display is still the same as before.
Uh, in the end,
Well, it's just the same.
the screen is still the same.
It's still a big change.
Um...
Basically,
the contact picture inside
does not have much change.
Then I will enter this simulation panel.
Uh...
The animation panel.
Then, use this recording to...
Uh,
I'm going to import this animation and do a simulation of it.
After I'm done with this step,
I'm going to export it to an ABC format.
After that, I'm going to go to the CCD.
Basically, the whole material is done.
I haven't talked about the material yet.
After I've set up the material,
I'll go to the UV panel
and arrange the UVs.
But, because the material in my project
is in the middle of the screen,
I can't see the details of the material.
So, I didn't do a detailed adjustment
to the proportion of the panels.
If you look at it from this angle,
the wind is a little bit small.
And the resolution in front of it is relatively large.
So, this is also based on the project.
And I made a little bit of a rough adjustment here.
After that,
I will import the adjusted material into SP
to give it a material rich.
Basically,
I'm going to add the cover,
the face mask inside,
and the parts that were divided before.
I'm going to add the material.
Then, there will be some small stains in the front.
There will be some logos in the back.
Then, after I export the material from here,
I will put all the things in CSD
to make a kindling.
That's it.
Let me show you.
Basically, it's at this stage.
I have a question that I'm very curious about.
Actually,
usually,
because I don't know,
how long have you been using Marvelous Designer?
It's been about
four or five years.
Do you think Marvelous Designer is important
in the process of making projects?
Marvelous Designer is still...
In the process of making projects,
it's a big part of it.
Because basically,
if we make this kind of material,
when we use this software,
it's very popular.
Before we use this,
we basically use some...
If you want to ask for good quality,
you can only use some brushstrokes
or carving methods in VB
to make this kind of thing.
Then,
of course,
I would say it's more like a competition.
But then,
Marvelous Designer started to become more and more popular.
Because at first,
I think it's actually...
It's a kind of clothing.
But I've seen a lot of big guys
using this software
to make some kind of games.
Including the one I played before.
I've seen that MD has also advertised it.
I think it's very effective.
And then,
I went to...
I started to get in touch with this software.
And then,
during this process,
I found that actually,
it made this problem very intuitive.
Usually,
at first,
before I started,
I thought that if I used this software,
it might be related to some...
Clothing board,
or some professional stuff related to clothing.
It's a deeper kind of knowledge.
But after I started using it,
I found that in fact,
this software,
whether it's the layout of the software,
or the functionality of this kind of planning,
it's actually very,
very easy to get started.
Basically, I just...
I started to...
Later on,
I started to rely more on this software.
It's like,
it quickly produces some
material effects.
It's actually very realistic.
And then...
Yes.
And then, this project,
actually,
it's equivalent to the first time
I used MD for this project.
I used MD for this...
For the simulation part.
I didn't do this animation before,
but the result is actually very good.
And then...
Yes.
And then, basically,
sometimes,
if you're making some static models,
the model,
sometimes,
it will lead the four sides out of here.
And then,
put it in the DB,
and use the brush to make some details.
It's also a...
It's a better base and foundation.
And then,
it's mainly because
its operation is very intuitive.
It can be used,
including...
I think it should be the new version.
It didn't exist before.
In 3D mode,
it can be used directly
for the simulation,
or something like that.
Yes.
And then...
This is because...
Because this problem,
actually,
like 3D simulation,
this problem is...
Well,
more users will respond.
Because,
some friends of CG,
well,
they may not know
the model very well.
If you let them
simulate it in the 2D window,
it will often have some
simulation problems.
So,
we will add
the 3D simulation...
3D.
Yes.
The 3D simulation tool.
And then,
this is something that
I can tell you in advance.
Well,
today,
let's see the benefits
of the live streamers.
Well,
we...
Marvel's Designer 11
may be released
in October.
And then,
there will be
a new feature,
which is 3D editing.
That is,
you can directly
edit the length
of a line
in the 3D window,
and the width
of a costume.
Like this.
Oh,
I see.
Sometimes...
Because...
It's okay.
You say it.
Sometimes,
for example,
you want to change
the width of your shoulder,
and the length
of your clothes.
Or,
sometimes,
you want to make
your waist
wider or narrower.
And then,
you want to adjust
it in the 2D window.
It may not be
intuitive enough.
So,
now,
we are planning
to release a new feature,
which is that
you can directly
adjust the width
and the width
of these lines
in the 3D window.
We are sure
that this feature
will be added.
So,
let's talk about it
in advance.
Yes,
there will be such a feature.
And then,
you will also use
this version of NMD.
Okay, okay.
I feel that
this is actually
quite practical.
Because,
most of us
are used to
using
NMD.
Because,
for myself,
I actually
didn't have
any idea
about the board
before.
After I got to know
NMD,
I started to get familiar with it.
And then,
including
some of the
3D operations
behind it,
it's very intuitive.
Yes.
Oh,
the 4D picture
in the 3D window.
I don't
really
understand
this.
I mean,
do you hope
to see
the 4D picture
in the 3D window
at the same time
as the 4D picture
in the 4D picture
in the 4D picture?
Because,
I saw
some comments
asking about
the 4D picture
in the 3D window.
So,
for those
in the CG industry,
do you think
you can
choose
some windows
by yourself?
For example,
I want to open
several 3D windows,
and then,
maybe I can
see its policy
at the same time.
Is this
useful
for everyone?
Because,
because,
the 4D picture
is,
because I don't use
a lot of 3D software
in my daily life.
So,
the 4D picture
that everyone
is talking about,
if I understand
it correctly,
you can see
the front,
back,
and side,
right?
Yes,
I think
the 4D picture
they are talking about
is similar to
3D Max
or
Maya CCD,
where you can
directly
try several things
at the same time.
Oh,
well,
I can tell you
in advance,
in Marvelous Designer 11,
you can open
multiple 3D windows
and multiple
2D windows
at the same time.
That is,
you can set
the position
yourself,
for example,
the front
or the back.
You can open
multiple windows
at the same time.
Then,
you can
change the layout
of Marvelous Designer 11.
You can
continuously
add new windows
and
continuously
select
the front
or the back,
or the top,
and so on.
You can switch
the 4D picture
yourself.
This can also be
revealed in advance
to everyone.
Similar to
the custom UI,
right?
Anyway,
when it comes to
Marvelous Designer 11,
there is no
right-hand corner
switch
mode.
This one,
right?
Yes,
this one is
all gone.
All of them
have become windows.
You can adjust
them yourself.
Yes,
it is very intuitive
and convenient
to have
multiple
screens
like this.
Yes,
yes,
yes.
Teacher,
can you remember?
Yes,
I can remember
what functions
there are
in Marvelous Designer 11.
Yes,
yes,
yes.
I have one question.
I used
the UV layout
before.
There is a
function
in the UV layout
that allows you
to automatically
display
all of
the UV
you have
displayed.
Will there
be such
function
in the future?
Because
when I
design
a new
version,
if there are
too many
parts,
I need
to place them
one by one.
Yes,
I am thinking
that if there is
such an automatic
layout,
the efficiency
will increase
quite quickly.
At the moment,
we do not seem
to have
an automatic
layout
plan.
But I can
mention
a function
development
requirement.
Generally,
when I design
UV,
I place
the UV
on the
2D window
and
the 3D window
is on the
1D window.
I can use
that function
directly.
Yes,
I can use
that function
directly.
Then,
I can apply
for the function
development requirement
for this automatic
layout,
but it may not
come out
so quickly.
I see.
Only lazy people
like me
will ask
this kind
of requirement.
Actually,
this requirement
may have been
mentioned
by previous
people
in the
previous
video.
Yes,
but now
some of
our
viewers
are also
asking
for this
function
development
requirement.
Okay,
I understand.
Then,
let me
think
if there
is anything
else.
Then,
I will
continue
this process
and talk
about it.
In the future,
I will
introduce
a blueprint
for the
client
in the background
and
make the
final
texture
for the
blueprint.
Then,
basically
the
final
is
like this
after
the
whole
fabric
is finished.
Then,
the
final
texture
will be
like this.
The production
process of
this helmet
is not related
to this MD,
so I won't
talk about it.
It's like the
modeling of
this helmet.
Then,
the last step
will be
basically to
take out
all the
relay needles
and then
make the
final
composition
in the
AE.
Then,
some
extended
KV or something
like that.
Then,
basically
it's
like this.
Then,
let's see
if there are
any other
questions
that we
need to know
about
this process.
Do you
have any
questions
for
Mr.
Houbo?
You can
put them
in the
chat box.
Thank you,
everyone.
Mr.
Houbo.
Thank you,
everyone.
Then,
we will
have
a
quick
Q&A
session
and
then
we'll
return
to
the
meeting
later.
Thank you,
everyone.
Mr.
Houbo.
The processor is an i7 6850K
The graphics card is a 3090
The memory is a 64
I have another question
The difference between GPU and CPU is quite big
GPU might have some differences
That's why I switched to CPU
Because the GPU is not fully developed yet
It's not mature yet
Yes, it's not mature yet
The resolution of different graphics cards is different
For example, the resolution of graphics cards is very fast
But when the resolution is very fast, it will be unstable
Because it has to calculate the particle collision
Yes, yes
It may have something to do with the speed of operation
I understand
And GPU simulation
Because we are still in the process of optimization
So when the particle diameter of the board
For example, when your particle diameter is 5
Your collision thickness
That is, the air thickness around the board
Also try to get close to this value
For example, when your particle diameter is 3
Your collision thickness can be reduced
You can reduce it to 3 or 2
Oh, I understand
Because GPU simulation
The biggest problem is
It will lead to layers and layers of collision
For example, your whole clothes
When they belong to the same layer
It may not be so
There will be some unstable places
But for example, if you make two or three layers of clothes
There may be some penetration problems
At this time, you may need to manually adjust its layers
For example
For example, drag the board
There are also some
That is to say, select the grid
Turn it over, etc.
Just have to deal with these boards first
And that is to say
When you usually use GPU simulation
Because GPU simulation
It's not that mature
So maybe GPU simulation
It's just a replacement in the process
And then in the end
If you really actually output
One of our final products
Maybe you still have to switch to
That CPU simulation
CPU
Yes, temporary simulation
Like this
Yes, yes, I understand
Uh, and then the shoes are also made by MD
The shoes are in the CCD
Uh, made of modeling
This is made of modeling in the CCD
Oh, and then
The Saibot helmet is carved in ZBrush
Or
Uh, the process of the helmet is like this
That is
Uh, I'm basically going to be in ZBrush
First carve a rough film
And then it's basically about some
Uh, big body blocks
After that
Then I will put it in this
Uh, in the CCD
To give it a top
Uh, I'm going to hide this first
This is
Uh
A model of the top
And then after flattening
It's probably like this
And then after I get this model
I'll put it in this
In the 3D
To give it
Uh, some details on it
The details of the surface of the cloth
And then
Uh, put it in the CCD
To give it a program-based material
Uh, the size of the bag model
To
ZB and MD
Is
Uh, mm
It should be
Oh, warning warning
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry
Sorry
Uh, I'll just say it with my mouth
That is
I usually
I don't seem to pay too much attention to the size
I usually jump over it by default
And then
It seems that when it comes to ZB
I can't remember clearly
It seems to be a bit of a problem when it comes to ZB
That is, its size
Will become very exaggerated
And then I usually go to
I go to CCD more
I think it should be normal to go to CCD
Uh, what does the teacher use ZB for?
I use it
Uh, the entry version of Wacom
Uh, about
A few hundred dollars, I think
Uh, it seems that the teacher is in MD
The advantage of finishing first
This part
Yes, it's MD
It's equivalent to when you're doing it
It's equivalent to already
Because it's from the beginning
Because it starts from the surface
It's equivalent to this part
It's already a UV
And then at the end of this UV panel
Just put it in this
Just line it up a little bit
Uh, that's fine
Do you have any other questions?
Um
Um, about the unit
It's actually because MD units are system-setting units
And then it includes how you import and export
It's all set up
So sometimes you might want to
A little bit of information
For example, you might be the whole software
The units used are all 5.5
But we defaulted
The unit when exporting may be mm
Or is it
Uh, yes, it may be mm
And then when you export
Maybe the value is too big
Or the number is too small
It's all possible to affect other software units
So the best thing is
When you import and export
You have to align the units
Including when you import
You have to align the units you choose
Mm
Mm, I see
Uh
Because I used to
Have a lot of two-dimensional drawing experience
So sometimes
From the perspective of art
I just
Sometimes I just look at the end result
Sometimes the parameters
I actually remember
Are not particularly clear
And then
Uh, it's just
Sometimes I just look at the end result
I think it's basically okay
Just let it be like this
Yeah
Mm
And then
Uh, UV panel
How to import PS to edit
Uh, I remember there was one in the UV panel
This
Um, I think he might be asking
Import to SP
He might be
PS
He might be playing back
Oh, yeah
Yeah
Do we need to make the M.D.
Hats
With
Or
To match
Uh
With
The
Hats
To match
With
Or
To match
With
The
UC
I
I basically
Uh
Just
In the M.D.
I didn't add any texture to it.
I added a more detailed texture in the SP.
This time, it might have some specific requirements,
so I used this process.
Sometimes it's a bit violent.
Sometimes I just went straight to CCC to make the program texture.
Let's see if there are any other questions.
If there are any questions,
you can ask them in the comments.
MD made the model thickness,
how do you deal with it?
How do you deal with the thickness you mentioned?
Do you need to remove it,
or adjust the thickness, or what?
I think he's probably just...
I think he's probably just asking...
Because some of my friends,
they might be MD,
they just go straight to the thin material,
and then go to CCC to adjust the thickness.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, I understand.
I understand.
I usually deal with it like this.
If the material itself is visually thinner,
like a piece of cloth or silk or something like that,
I might just pour it out directly.
It has a hook selection.
This thick one.
I'll hook this in.
It will fall in.
It will have a very weak thickness.
But sometimes,
like some fabrics,
for example,
like Yu Yongfu,
it might be...
It's obvious that it feels like
there's a thickness of fillings in it.
I might just,
on the basis of this fabric,
give it an outer layer or an inner layer,
and then give it a little more pressure,
and then let it form a...
It's sewed together,
and there's a feeling of filling in the middle.
That's about it.
Yeah.
Also,
because there are some friends
who have questions about
how Malu's designer
went to CD or Maya
to make some adjustments
to the thickness of the follow-up.
So we're also recording a video like this right now.
After that,
we'll probably share it on our official Bilibili account.
It's about how to combine
AMD and other 3D devices together
and use it together.
So we don't have to bother...
I understand.
Yeah, so we don't have to bother everyone.
Like,
all the teachers might have to explain to the users.
We'll be releasing an official video soon.
Okay.
Yeah.
Let's see if everyone has any other questions.
If you have any questions,
or want to know more,
you can post them in the chat.
Okay.
I'm very curious.
Teacher,
how long does it take you to make
a set of clothes like this
in Malu's designer?
Like,
not including the parts
that need to be modified in the later stages.
For example,
Well,
if it's not about
the customer's modifications,
and it's me
who has to do it from the beginning,
it's actually very fast.
It takes a few hours to make it.
Because mine isn't that complicated.
It's just
very,
very simple.
Like,
some bags,
and this kind of...
It's just...
And it doesn't have a specific structure
that makes it seem like
there's some kind of
difference.
So mine is
made
relatively fast.
It takes about
a few hours,
three or four hours,
or even two or three hours.
For example,
for the first version,
this kind of material
might...
This kind of
shape,
this kind of effect,
can be done in about
two or three hours.
Anyway,
this one
is pretty fast.
This kind of
presentation
effect.
This one
can be done
very quickly.
The main thing is that
there are a lot of
special features
added to it.
Like this
zipper.
In the past,
you might
need to
go to
the ZB
to do
some
detailed effects.
But the back...
I think this zipper
should also be
added to the new features
at the back.
If I remember correctly.
Yes.
So when I
did this part,
it was very cool
when I did it.
Basically,
pull this line
and the zipper
will automatically
appear.
It's very convenient.
Yes.
We also use
this function
quite often.
Let me take a look
at the chat.
The chat is saying...
Learning how to
stick your head out,
right?
This...
The more you stick out,
the stronger it is,
right?
This seems to be
your stick out
and your
strong point
are the same.
Let me see.
I see the chat
is saying
you can remove
the pattern
in the clothing section.
Well,
I don't think
this is the plan
at the moment
because this is
in relation to
the anti-activation section.
How much is
the cost
of the MD project?
Why would anyone
ask this kind of question?
Is this...
Is this possible?
The cost of
the MD project?
Are you talking about
the whole project
or
the MD...
How do we divide
this part?
We must
do it
for the whole project.
After the MD
top
is replaced,
why do we
have to
redo it?
After the MD
top
is replaced?
Oh,
I know.
He is asking
about the top
inside the
Motherless Designer.
Oh.
Yes,
you may have
chosen
the new
version of
the Cologne
and if it is replaced,
it doesn't need to be
replaced.
It is not necessary
to replace
the MD.
So,
we can
put the specific
project
to
the
Cologne
Technology Support Group
to check it.
Because
there is no
project file,
I am not sure
whether there is
a bug
in the function
or something.
Because the top
is,
in the Motherless Designer,
there are
few people
who
do this
in the MD.
So,
I don't know.
Does the MD
hire people?
Well,
they used to
but now
it is
too late.
It is too late
but
in fact,
there are only
two people
in the MD
in China.
Except me,
there is
a chicken.
So,
actually,
next year,
there may be
a plan
to hire
people.
But,
this year,
it seems
that
the MD
is not
going to
be
able to
work
in the MD.
So,
I don't know
if
there is
a plan
to hire
people
but
this year
is
the best
time
for me
to have
a MD.
It is
the best
time
for me
to have
a MD.
There is no UV in Marvelous Designer, so you can use 3D lines to draw some lines that can be seen in Marvelous Designer.
Because there is no UV, people usually don't choose the unified UV when they export.
Because some friends may be in Marvelous Designer directly.
In this case, if you choose the unified UV when you export, the bright line cannot be exported.
Because the bright line's UV is empty, it has no UV.
So the bright line can only be exported in the form of white mold.
So sometimes friends may wonder why the bright line appears only in the form of texture,
but not in the form of mold.
In fact, the main reason is that when you export, you choose the unified UV.
That is, when you export, you don't have to choose that option.
You can export the bright line directly from the white mold.
So when you export, you don't have to choose.
Maybe your subsequent UV, or you don't have to export the texture first.
Export a bright line.
And then just delete the other version.
What about the self-made panel pattern?
Let me think about how to talk about it.
In the future, we may do some internal model library optimization.
There is no need to go to the official website to download it.
But there is also a module library.
In Marvelous Designer,
there is a module library on the left.
There are also some pre-made clothing modules in it.
It can also be used and operated repeatedly.
Oh, my toothache is finally over.
I can finally take off the ice bag.
Now I'm finally free.
The more I talk about it, the more excited I am.
Suddenly I found that it doesn't hurt.
Oh, MD's creation tool has been completed.
After completion, the right arrow is replaced.
Then the line is gone.
Well, maybe this...
Oh, I know.
Maybe this function is like this.
So I will only go to this library at the end.
Currently, the library...
To be honest, it is still more recommended to go to other software.
Don't go to Marvelous Designer.
After that, it may be...
I remember that the next version will be optimized for this function.
In the development, but the specific development...
Can it come out?
Not necessarily.
There were a lot of users before.
Can you add a zero mesh function to Marvelous Designer?
No.
It can't be added.
Zero mesh is the function of ZB.
Sometimes when I see such a problem, I think...
Then why don't we use ZB?
Why do we have to force our MD?
Every software has its own advantages.
Yes.
I think now most...
New users or old users...
The consensus with MD is actually quite strong.
They can understand that our software is just a non-monitoring software.
Non-monitoring.
Yes.
In fact, in the past,
For example, when I used another software in our company before,
I think it is different from the users who use MD.
That is to say, MD users...
MD users are really good at finding their own solutions.
If they think they can't do this in Marvelous Designer,
It's okay.
I won't force you Marvelous Designer.
I will find another software to solve this problem.
Can you create a face directly?
Create a face directly?
I don't know if you mean extension or something.
I remember that extension face can be extended by pressing Shift and Ctrl.
Then drag the line.
It should be able to extend the face directly.
But if you want to create a face,
You may need to add points manually.
Blender laughed.
He carried everything down.
There are often friends who compare our software with Blender's non-monitoring.
Then at this time, they will find that the leaves are professional.
Yes, I think every software has its own good points.
There are lots of software features that we really want to add.
But we don't have the skills to develop all of them.
I'm thinking about when I upload today's live stream, should I delete the part about the new features?
I don't want other people to hear it. I don't want my friends who are watching the live stream to hear it.
But the new version will be released soon.
October? The beginning of October?
We are also Marvelous.3's 2077.
We were supposed to release the new version at the beginning of this year.
Then we encountered a huge, huge bug.
In order to solve this bug, we developed all kinds of bugs.
A whole generation of bugs.
And we kept jumping and jumping and jumping.
We kept looking and looking until October.
Will Marvelous.3's 11 be on the rise?
I can only say...
I've heard that it's going to rise.
But it shouldn't have much to do with everyone.
Entrepreneurs will be on the rise.
Individuals won't be on the rise.
It's not hard. It's not hard.
It's not hard at all today.
I think it's going to be hard for Mr. Hotpot today.
Because he talks a lot.
No, no, no. It's just a normal sharing.
It's not hard. It's not hard.
Will MD be acquired in the future?
No, no, no. Our boss is very rich.
My boss MD is very rich.
The most common saying is,
We are rich.
Only MD is acquired by others.
No, no. Then we can't be acquired by others.
I'm afraid that...
I was talking to a friend earlier.
I was talking about MD acquiring Blender or something.
I was thinking, let us go.
Our MD...
You have to imagine that there are only two people in the MD China team.
Can we actually acquire other companies?
I'm crying.
What is the goal of your software?
Oh, I also know that.
Substance.
What is the goal of your software?
Our software has never been the goal of defeating other 3D software.
I think the 3D software...
The environment is that everyone must coexist.
Only coexist.
Because it's hard for a software to...
It's so comprehensive.
It includes some of the functions of other 3D software.
So after the 3D industry,
This software is definitely more and more biased.
It's the one I'm good at.
And then, it may also incorporate some of the functions of other software.
It may also incorporate some of the functions of other software.
But it's impossible to say that it will completely defeat another software.
I think this is unrealistic.
Yes, they are all complementary.
Why do we have to defeat other software?
And there is also the word to destroy Cloud.
Cloud is our brother's product.
We are in the same company.
I'm really unlucky tonight.
I just collided with their live broadcast.
Then I quietly moved from the fifth floor to the third floor.
See, our MB is just like this.
We are so in sync.
We were supposed to live broadcast on the fifth floor, but now we are on the third floor.
We are on the fifth floor, but now we are on the third floor.
Yes.
We said we would defeat Cloud.
I'm so happy to see the results.
No.
Our software in the future is not ready.
Our software is not ready.
As of now,, the blue platform is as much as possible.
As of now, the blue platform is as much as possible.
There are also some places that are compatible with other 3D software.
And the platform on NVIDIA
The platform developed by NVIDIA
We will also add it later
It's on that platform
To generate communication with other 3D software
There is no such plan for integrated T2 software
This can tell you completely
No no
Thank you for your attention
Yes, development towards CG
So don't say anymore
Marvelous Designer can't beat other software
We never want to beat other software
We have been self-sacrificing
I think sometimes people still imagine our company as a very large company
I didn't expect that our company is actually only a little bit
Blurring Preview
Now there is a dynamic blurring brush
You can use this
There are still some functions under the sculpting mode
Still very easy to use
Including you can use stamp first
To make some wrinkles
And then use the dynamic blurring brush to make it
Under the sculpting mode
But soon there will be no such mode
Because it will all become windows
My computer
Oh no, I can't give it to you in advance
Anyway, after that
MD's interface may have some changes
Some changes
Okay, do you have any other questions?
I'll give you two more minutes
9.45
Seven minutes
Let's see if you have any other questions
Teacher is also very hard
It's so late and you have to live with us
Hard work
No no
Not hard
Just normal sharing
We can share your stories
For example
When you don't care about being on stage
You also don't care about what you say
And we all share the same thoughts
We
We previously saw you
We also first saw you
On Behance
We saw some videos of you
For you
And
Yes
Because it was really
Very
Like
And there's also
I found out that a lot of people on the internet use the teacher's picture when they talk about cyberpunk.
They all use it, there are so many of them, do you know?
Because...
You say it, you say it.
No, no, you say it, you say it.
Because in the early days, cyberpunk started to become popular a long time ago.
But when it really came to China, everyone started to use this element in various ways.
It started in the last two years.
And then...
Because I used to be a fan of cyberpunk, I would definitely get into this style.
So after a few times in the project, there will be more and more customers who want to do this kind of style.
That is...
No matter if it was two years ago or now, it's still a very popular style.
Basically, everyone still wants to go with this style.
Yes.
I think it's mainly because of the style of cyberpunk.
What it's usually after is a high-profile, hard-working life.
Maybe people in real life are also more likely to get caught up in it.
Because some of the old science fiction, for example, some of the hard science fiction.
It may be...
It may be that the sense of being a person is not necessarily so realistic, so closely related to us.
That kind of function.
Or style.
When we look at cyberpunk, we will actually reflect more on the emotions in real life.
Or the life situation.
Yes.
But what impressed me most about the teacher was the space station, the space station.
In fact, it is not the style of cyberpunk.
Oh.
Yes.
I think the space station.
That one is very, very impressive.
I think because...
This one.
Yes.
I think it gives me a kind of...
No matter if it's the fabric or something else.
Because...
It's like when I used to watch Ace of Cards, when I saw Tien Ying playing Lieshi.
I have no resistance to all of these space stations and spacesuits.
I usually see works, I see something like this.
I will not resist.
Yes.
When I see stuff like this, I choose to have a look.
Actually, this piece is a very random product.
I can talk about how I made it.
At first, actually...
Just for the...
Because during that time I was learning the Moc3D software,
so I went to make a floor.
After putting the floor together,
I felt that it seemed to be interesting.
It's like this.
I thought I could create an environment, so I started building a wall.
After I finished building the wall, I thought I needed a ceiling, so I built it.
After I built the ceiling, I felt like there was a lack of people in the scene.
So I started to make an astronaut helmet.
Then I used Marble Is Dead to make some materials.
Because at that time, it was actually a relatively early time to get in touch with Marble Is Dead.
So I also made some materials while I was learning to make it.
There were some places on the wall that were still a bit of a mess at the time.
So I went to read some articles while I was making it.
Then I put it in the scene and gave it a theme.
It was a relatively random thing to produce.
But later on, it seemed to have...
It was a lot of work.
A lot of my friends responded that they really liked it.
So I was pretty surprised.
It was like a process of practice.
I finally made a work.
And I think your work has a very distinct feature.
All your colors are very matching.
It's amazing.
Really?
Yes, really.
I think it's...
But you know, I'm actually weak in color.
Oh, really?
I also have a friend around me.
It's been a long time since I've been on a live stream.
I started to look at mountains every time I go on a live stream.
I have a friend who is like that, too.
But he's amazing.
He's also weak in color.
He's also in the industry that's a little close to what we're doing now.
He's an advertising designer.
But I don't usually feel that I'm weak.
Actually, I don't think it really affects my life.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Anyway, it's...
When I was in college, I was always told by my teacher that my drawing was gray.
But then I found out that it didn't really affect my actual work.
Yeah.
And I think...
Now, people's taste in color has been quite popular recently.
It's not as saturated as it used to be.
It's relatively low saturated.
But I think it's okay to wear some black and white.
Anyway, now, people have diversified their taste in color and aesthetics.
It's not that you have to have a lot of contrast.
Wow, this is the first time I've heard that.
I don't think I can feel it at all.
In fact, it's hard to feel it when you look at works now.
You can feel what kind of character the person behind the work is.
But I really don't feel it when it comes to these details.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I get it.
Are the astronauts also made by AMD?
Yes.
The clothes of the astronauts are also made by AMD.
Including...
Let's look at this one.
It was all made by AMD before.
The astronauts seem to have done some...
It's going to give some pressure.
It's going to give it a kind of...
But actually, it's not quite reasonable later.
Because my hands...
My hands...
I didn't make the fabric.
Because I didn't use AMD to make the gloves.
So I used the model to make a copy.
Yeah.
Why can't I make the thickness of the fabric with AMD?
I actually gave it some pressure.
I gave it some pressure.
Is there a good way to do it?
You're late, right, baby?
I just did a demonstration
Yeah, I just did a demonstration
It's okay, you can watch the video after this
Also, there was a episode before
There were gloves in a few episodes before
What did I do in the last episode?
Oh, I did the protective suit
Also, there was a tutorial video about how to make gloves
You can wait for the video to be released
Oh, is it too late?
We're already at the end
It's a little late, baby
Let me think about it
I was thinking about it
Oh, right
I'm so lucky to have every teacher
I have to ask the teacher
How long have you used Marbleless Designer?
And then I ask
Every teacher uses it longer than me
Because when I used it in the early days
Anyway, when I used Marbleless Designer
Once I added it to my workflow
It never left me again
Basically, every time
As long as it involves this kind of
I will use this
Whether it's a competition
Or a video
Yes, it's the calculation itself
Or this sewing
It's actually very efficient at this speed
Thank you so much for your support
Our software
The main thing is that the software is really very useful
The helmet is
Oh, yes
The helmet is made by Mose and D
Thank you for coming to the live broadcast room tonight
To watch our live broadcast
Then we will see you next time
Bye bye
Okay, bye bye
Thank you, Teacher Li
Bye bye
Not hard, not hard
Bye bye everyone
Bye bye
Then I'll stop the live broadcast first
Bye bye everyone
Bye bye